原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     肉松  克里斯  RiverSide152  Eunice
翻译     吃冰棒  苏葵  杏仁斯嘉丽
翻译     Margaery  子V  joy_bwl
校对     喃喃
时间轴     啾啾啾  大葱
后期     8T
总监     喃喃
他拿枪威胁我父亲性命
He's got a gun... to my father's head.
我们先处理掉拉罗  然后我们再谈
We take care of Lalo. Then we'll talk.
灰色蒙特卡洛  一名男性驾驶
Gray Monte Carlo occupied by one male.
普韦布洛
我们口头达成了协议
We had a verbal agreement.
而凯文仍然能建成他的客服中心  所有人共赢
Kevin still gets his call center. Everybody wins.
我受不了了
I can't do this anymore.
我们都在撒谎
You lie! I lie!
要么我们现在就结束这段关系
Either we end this now...
就怎样
Or what?
要么我们就...
Or maybe...
要么我们就结婚
Maybe we get married.
过去的旧帐
And anything that already happened...
我们就不翻了
we're not going back over all that.
只着眼于今后的事
Let's just focus on from here on out.
没错  过去的都过去了
Right. Past is past.
向前看
And moving forward...
如果我想隐瞒你一些事
Uh, if I have the urge to not tell you something,
我还是得告诉你
then I've gotta tell you.
没错  完全披露[诚实]Right. Full disclosure.
-我俩都是吗  -我俩都是
- And it works both ways? - Works both ways.
静音了
And... mute.
如果我想隐瞒你一些事
Okay, what if I have the urge to not tell you something,
但我说了
but I tell you,
惹你不高兴怎么办
and you don't like what you hear?
我只想知道怎么回事
I just want to know what's going on.
是  但
Yeah, but --
吉米  船到桥头自然直
Jimmy, we'll cross that bridge when we come to it.
他来了
There he is.
我们真的要这么做吗
So, we're really doing this, huh?
似乎是的
Yeah, looks that way.
我迟到了吗
Am I late?
-没  -好
- Nope. - ‭Cool.
早安
Mornin'.
-谢谢过来  -很高兴见到你
- Thanks for coming. - Good to see you.
-走吧  -行
- Shall we? ‭- Yeah.
怎么了
What's up?
需要我帮你保管戒指吗
Want me to hold the rings for you?
没有戒指
Oh, there's no rings.
这好办
Well, I can fix that easy.
楼下有个职员
I seen a clerk downstairs.
他有个好钻戒
He had a nice rock,
应该有半克拉
probably about a half a carat.
休  不
Huell, no.
这不是干那种事
This is a different kind of thing.
这样啊
Oh. It's like that.
那我们该做全套  为了你俩的孩子
Then we should do it up right, then, for the rugrat.
没有孩子
No, there's no rugrat.
那你至少得带她去度假吧
Well, you're at least gonna take her somewhere after this?
小蜜月
Little honeymoon?
我有一个在罗斯威尔开旅馆的朋友
I gotta friend ‭who runs a B&B in Roswell.
给你优惠
Get you a good deal.
还是下次再说吧
How about we take a raincheck on that?
我们得尽快把这事办好
We just need to get this done.
你懂吗
You feel me?
这是法律上的安排
This is a legal arrangement.
这样的话  如果我有麻烦了
This way, if I get into trouble,
他们就不能逼她指证我
they can't make her testify against me.
你们为了这个结婚
You getting hitched for that?
没错
Yeah.
没错  就是因为这个
Yeah. That's all this is.
你懂了吗
You got it?
她姓麦吉尔还是古德曼
She gonna be a McGill or Goodman?
韦克斯勒
Wexler.
我去办事了
I-I got to go finish this.
给
Here you go.
詹姆斯·M·麦吉尔  金柏莉·韦克斯勒
谢谢
Thanks.
先生  你带了前两次离婚的文件吗
Sir, do you have documentation of your two previous dissolutions?
带了
Yeah.
好  稍等
Great. One sec.
你没意见吧
This okay with you?
当然
Of course.
嗯
Yeah.
我就是...
I just mean, um...
这可能不像你十二岁时梦想的那样
this might not be what you dreamed of when you were 12.
吉米  跟那没关系
Jimmy, it's not about that.
这只是...
This is just, you know...
-我们谈过的  -对
- everything we talked about. - ‭Right.
对  我知道
Right. I know.
就是确认一下
Just making sure.
都好了
All set.
再给我二十五块
I just need $25.
我来吧
I got it.
结婚证
结婚仪式  一切从简
抱歉久等了
Sorry to keep you waiting.
今天挺忙的
Been that kind of day.
韦克斯勒和麦吉尔
So...Wexler-McGill?
对
Yes.
你们选了短誓词  对吧
And you picked the short vows, that right?
对
Yes.
有见证人吗
And you have your witnesses?
那好了
Okay, then.
开始吧
Here we go.
开始了
"詹姆斯·摩根·麦吉尔
"Do you, James Morgan McGill,
你是否愿意娶金柏莉·韦克斯勒"
take Kimberly Wexler to --"
没中间名
Hmm. No middle name.
"成为你的合法妻子
"To be your lawfully wedded wife?
从今天起  执子之手
To have and to hold, from this day forward,
无论顺境或是逆境
for better, for worse,
贫穷或是富有
for richer, for poorer,
健康或是疾病
in sickness and in health,
直到死亡将你们分开"
till death do you part?
我愿意
I do.
"金柏莉·韦克斯勒
"And do you, Kimberly Wexler,
你是否愿意嫁给詹姆斯·摩根·麦吉尔
take James Morgan McGill
成为你的合法丈夫
to be your lawfully wedded husband?
从今天起  执子之手
To have and to hold, from this day forward,
无论顺境或是逆境
for better, for worse,
贫穷或是富有
for richer, for poorer,
健康或是疾病
in sickness and in health,
直到死亡将你们分开"
till death do you part?"
我愿意
I do.
你们准备戒指了吗
Do you have the rings?
我们...
We, um --
我们不做那一套
We didn't do that.
没有戒指
No rings.
好嘞
Okey-dokey.
"以新墨西哥州
"Then by the power vested in me
赋予我的权力
by the state of New Mexico,
我现在宣布你们结为夫妻"
I now pronounce you husband and wife."
"你们可以亲吻了"
"You may kiss."
再来一次
One more, one more.
绝命律师
第五季  第七集
一起吃午餐没戏了吗
So, lunch is definitely out?
抱歉  我脱不开身
Sorry. I-I just can't get away.
但今晚我会早点回家
But I'll be home early tonight.
我也是
Me too.
索尔·古德曼  为你火速伸张正义
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you!
我一直在给你打电话
I been calling you.
我早上很忙
Yeah. I had a busy morning.
去拘留所
Go to lock-up.
有个委托人在等你
Client's waiting for you.
我的"委托人"
My "Client"? Wha--
这次谁又被抓了
Who got picked up this time?
豪尔赫·德古兹曼
Jorge De Guzman.
豪尔赫·德古兹曼是谁
Who the hell is Jorge De Guzman?
你觉得呢
Who do you think?
豪尔赫·德古兹曼公诉案
State vs. Jorge De Guzman.
案件编号CR-2004003022
Case CR-2004003022.
德古兹曼先生
Mr. De Guzman.
一级谋杀罪
Murder in the first degree,
持械抢劫
robbery while armed with a deadly weapon,
篡改证据  纵火
tampering with evidence, arson --
法官大人  我的委托人
Your Honor, uh, my client waives
放弃剩余指控的宣读
the reading ‭of the remaining charges.
他有何辩护
How does he plead?
所有指控均宣称无罪
"Not guilty" on all charges.
我想在六周之后安排预审听证会
I'd like to schedule a pre-trial hearing in six weeks.
并且拒绝被告保释
And I'm going to deny bond.
法官大人
Your Honor --
这是我的决定
That's my decision.
谢谢你抽空与我们见面
Thank you for making time for us on such short notice.
我们想当面告诉你
We wanted to tell you face-to-face
律所里的所有人
how much everyone in the firm
都为昨天发生的事感到遗憾
regrets what happened yesterday.
图克姆卡里的情况完全失控
The situation in Tucumcari spiraled out of control,
对此我们负全责
and we take full responsibility.
凯文  你选了我当你的律师
Kevin, you chose me as your attorney.
那是我职业生涯中最美好的一天
And that was the best day of my professional life.
昨天是我职业生涯中最可怕的一天
Yesterday was the worst day of my professional life.
我无法表达让你失望的歉意
I can't tell you how much I regret that I let you down.
但我想让你知道  如果你选择
But I want you to know that, if you choose
继续与我和律所进行合作
to move forward with me and with us,
这种事不会再发生第二次
nothing like that will ever happen again.
事情出了差错  这不可否认
No one's denying ‭that things went off course,
但我们应该记得  过去的一年半里
but let's keep in mind that over the last 18 months,
我们开设了二十四家新分行
we've opened 24 new branches.
在图克姆卡里之前
And, until Tucamcari,
法律方面的工作一直完美无缺
the legal work has been...flawless.
金  你掉链子了  这没得说
Kim, you dropped the ball. That's for sure.
凭借你的才智
And, uh with all your smarts,
还有一整个办公室的高学历同事
whole office full of associates and fancy degrees...
你居然被一个...
you get rolled over by...
你知道怎么回事
Well, you know what happened.
我本来对你的期望更高
I expected more.
感谢你们的到来
Thanks for coming in.
谢谢你  凯文
Thank you, Kevin.
-佩奇  -谢谢
- Paige. - ‭Thank you.
金  还有一件事
Kim, one more thing.
这个家伙  叫麦吉尔还是古德曼  随便吧
This fella -- McGill or Goodman, whatever.
你可以找个更好的
You could do a whole lot better.
我觉得五五开吧  但至少我们试了
I'll say 50/50, but we gave it a shot.
里奇  我们不能就这样走了
Rich, we can't leave it like this.
他会纠结一段时间  到时候再看结果吧
Oh, he'll stew for a bit, and then we'll see.
如果他继续和我们合作了  那怎么办
And if he does stick with us, then what?
我们要一直如履薄冰下去吗
We walk on eggshells forever?
我们还有别的选择吗
What's our alternative?
我们反驳了  是吗
We countered with seven, right?
没错  但是在经过调查后
Yes, but after the survey --
抱歉打扰了
Uh, sorry to interrupt.
介意我们再占用几分钟时间吗
Do you mind if we take just another minute of your time?
可以
I guess.
凯文  无论我们接下来的关系看起来如何
Kevin, no matter what our relationship looks like moving forward,
我们欠你一个事实
we owe you the truth.
事实就是  你无视了我们的建议
And the truth is, you ignored our advice.
这成我的错了
Oh, so this is my fault.
我们说过  梅萨维德
We said Mesa Verde
应该重新考虑客服中心的地址
should reconsider the site for the call center.
你拒绝了
You declined.
我们建议你保留成交的土地  作为投资
We advised you to keep the purchased lot as an investment.
你也拒绝了
You declined.
我们还建议你离开会议
And we advised you to leave that meeting
因为对方在谈判过程中明显要进行敲诈
when it became apparent that the other side was negotiating in bad faith.
你还是拒绝了
You declined.
我们在每一步都给了你最好的指导
At every point, we gave you the best guidance we could,
但每次你都选择自行其是
and at every point, you chose to go your own way.
我们是你的律师
We are your attorneys,
给你建议是我们的职责
and it is our job to advise you.
做决定的人永远是你
The decisions will always be yours,
但如果你继续无视我们的建议
but...if you continue to ignore us...
那我们就不该合作
then this is the wrong relationship.
还有  凯文  我必须告诉你
And, Kevin, I have to tell you,
以后不管谁做你的律师
whoever represents you in the future...
我希望你多听取他们的意见
I hope you're gonna listen to them a little bit better.
说完了吗
That it?
那好吧
Alright, then.
周四见
See you on Thursday.
好
Okay.
我们...就不打搅了
Well, uh...I guess we'll get out of your hair.
周四
Thursday.
JMM
JMM.
那是什么
What's that?
是我的座右铭
Oh, that's my motto.
是吗
Yeah?
"公正最重要"
"Justice Matters Most."
好  说重点
Okay, brass tacks.
"德古兹曼"这身份有多可信
Um, how solid is this "De Guzman" thing?
如果他们发现你的真实身份
Because if they find out you're not who they think you are,
-那可能会有点...  -这不会是问题
- that could be a little -- - It's not gonna be a problem.
很好
Great!
首先
Um, first up,
我们得把谋杀指控减轻为过失杀人
we got to get the murder rap down to manslaughter.
我认为地检准备和你谈认罪协议
Now, I think that the DA is primed to cut a deal.
让他们主动提出  争取主动...
So I say make 'em come to us, power move --
-不  -不
- No. - ‭No?
不  不谈协议
Nope. No deal.
要是闹到庭审的话...
Here's the thing about going to trial --
不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.
不上庭  不谈协议
No trial. No deal.
好吧  没问题  只是...
Okay, yeah. Sure. Just...
你有什么高见
What did you have in mind?
你先把我保出去
You're gonna get me out on bail.
保释
Bail?
这...
That's...
那边的规矩...
Well, the thing there --
我不知道边界以南的办事规矩
I mean, I don't know how things work south of the border,
但这里  在这种情况下
but here, ‭under these circumstances,
希望渺茫
uh, well, that's a long shot.
你想和贩毒集团交朋友吗
Quieres ser amigo de el cartel?
不好意思  我不懂...
I'm sorry. I-I don't, uh...
你想和贩毒集团交朋友吗
You wanna be a friend of the cartel?
你该换新座右铭了
Time to get yourself a new motto.
挣钱最重要
Just. Make. Money.
"但'朝生暮死'是什么意思"
"'But what does that mean, "Ephemeral"?'
小王子追问道
repeated the little prince,
他这个人一有问题
who never in his life let go of a question
就要刨根问底
once he had asked it.
"意思是
'It means,
'有很快会消失的危险'"
"Which is in danger of speedy disappearance."'
"我的花有很快会消失的危险吗"
'Is my flower in danger of speedy disappearance?'
"毫无疑问"
'It certainly is.'"
好了  孩子  剩下的以后再读
Okay, kid, ‭we'll finish the rest later.
现在该说晚安了
Now, good night.
不要嘛  爷爷
Not yet, Pop-pop.
再读两页
Just two more pages.
就两页  然后睡觉  好吗
Two more pages, and that's it, alright?
你躺下吧
Now lie down.
"我的花朝生暮死"
"'My flower is ephemeral,'
小王子喃喃自语道
the little prince said to himself,
"而且她只有四根刺
'and she only has four thorns
来抵御这个世界的侵害"
to defend herself against the world."
她睡着了
She's out.
应该是《小王子》的功劳
Think "The Little Prince" did the trick.
我觉得是你跟她玩捉迷藏把她累坏了
I think you wore her out with all that hide-and-seek.
我说不好
I don't know.
也许是她把我累坏了
I think maybe she wore me out.
我有一个女同事
This girl at work --
她不知道怎么哄儿子睡觉
she can't get her son to sleep.
那孩子两岁了
The kid's 2 years old,
半夜还在大闹天宫
and he's still tearing around the house at midnight.
马蒂就是那样
Matty was like that.
真的吗
Really?
嗯  真的
Yeah, really.
一直不消停
Never wanted to conk out.
闹死人
‭Too busy.
他真可爱
He was such a cutie.
我很喜欢他坐在圣诞老人腿上的照片
I love those pictures of him sitting on Santa's lap.
那小脸
Ahh, that face.
大哭不止  每年如此
Cried his eyes out. Every year.
但每到第二年  他都想再试一试
And every year, he'd want to try it again.
我现在好些了
I'm better now.
发生什么了
What changed?
我决定面对现实
Decided to play the cards I was dealt.
他就说周四例会上见
Just said he'll see us at the regular Thursday meeting.
你对当权者说了真话
You spoke truth to power.
那就看看他会不会听了
We'll see if he sticks to it.
你今天怎么样
How'd your day go?
我结婚了
I got married.
过来
Here.
怎么了
What?
我想隐瞒你一件事
I'm having the urge not to tell you something.
不是什么大事
It's nothing.
我晚点告诉你  好吗
I'll -- ‭I'll tell you later, okay?
吉米  等等  等等
Jimmy, wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
什么事
What?
我有一个新客户
I have a -- a new client.
他有些关系
He's, um, connected.
我是说  他是贩毒集团的
I mean, he's a cartel guy.
墨西哥那边的
From Mexico.
级别挺高
Pretty high up.
不管怎样  他因谋杀被捕
Anyway, he's in for murder,
想获得保释
and he wants bail, which --
这根本不可能
That's impossible.
这家伙永远也不可能重见天日了
I mean...no way in hell this dude is ever seeing sunshine.
但如果我可以  想办法...
But if I could, you know, somehow find a way...
他说了  我可以成为贩毒品集团的朋友
um...he said, uh, I'd be a friend of the cartel.
"贩毒集团的朋友"
"Friend of the cartel"?
你知道这意味着什么
You know what that means.
意味着钱
Means money.
像蒙大拿州农场主一样有钱
Ranch in Montana kind of money,
可以买得起自己的私人飞机
like, uh, private jet kind of money
出席记者招待会
press conferences,
上电视  等等
TV news, the works.
但是...
But...
你想成为贩毒集团的朋友吗
do you want to be a friend of the cartel?
不  不
No. No.
当然不了  我...
Absolutely not. I...
不管怎样  八字还没一撇
Anyway, it's a moot point
因为这个人潜逃风险极高  所以...
'cause the guy's the definition of a flight risk, so...
我准备好好为他辩护  就是做做样子
Look, I'm gonna put up a fight, right, just for show.
不可能有法官会批准他的保释
There's no judge on earth that's gonna grant him bail.
只是  我想对你隐瞒这件事
I just -- ‭I didn't want to tell you,
所以我觉得我应该告诉你
so I thought I should tell you.
你知道吗
You know what?
什么
What?
很高兴你跟我说了
I'm glad you did.
好了  回你的牢房去
Alright, back in your cell!
不  不  我没事  我没事
No, no. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
第六街是怎么回事
So, what's happening with sixth street?
赚了多少
And the take?
好
Okay.
你准备怎么办
So, what're you gonna do about it?
准备把疯子小八弄进来吗
You gonna send in Ocho Loco?
那更好
Oh. Even better. Nice.
听着
Listen.
我有件事要交给你去办
I got something for you to do.
不谈谈我爸的事  我什么都不会告诉你的
I'm not telling you shit until we talk about my dad.
你要告诉我什么以及你什么时候说
What you tell me and when you say it
这由不得你
is not up to you.
你说当拉罗出局后
Listen, you said ‭when Lalo's out of the picture,
我们就能谈谈我父亲  对吧
we'll talk about my father, right?
他现在出局了
Well, ‭he's out of the picture.
你说吧
Say your piece.
我不干了
I'm done.
我想退出
I want out.
你想让我帮你跟弗林划清界限
And you want me to square it with Fring.
不只是弗林  还有贩毒集团
Fring's not all of it. It's the cartel.
我一消失
I disappear,
他们就会去对付我父亲
they're gonna go after my father.
他得跟我一起走
He's gotta come with me.
但无论我跟他说什么
But no matter what I say,
他都叫我去找警察
with him it's the cops or nothing.
但警察解决不了这事
The cops won't solve this.
你有办法吗
You got a way?
你还有什么没告诉我
What are you holding out?
罗拉从里面给我打电话了
Lalo called me from inside.
他让我重新掌权
He put me back in charge.
然后呢
And...?
然后
And...
他希望我烧毁一家洛博罗炸鸡
he wants me to burn down a Pollos Hermanos.
那他就没有出局  对吧
Then he's not out of the picture, is he?
"牛油果风暴"的活动促销
The "Avocado mania" promotion,
在我们挑选的几个分店试行后
which we've been testing in select franchises,
取得了卓佳的效果
has been a smashing success,
为所有参与的分店提高了18%的进店客流量
contributing to an 18% increase in foot traffic at participating locations
并提升了12%的消费者满意度
and a 12% bump ‭in customer satisfaction.
我们一眼就知道这是个机遇
We know a good thing when we see it,
所以我们决定于第二季度全面推出"牛油果风暴"
so we are planning to fully roll out "Avocado mania" in Q2.
另外  我们改革后的"家庭欢乐聚餐"
Additionally, our innovative "Family-fun" remodel
提升了胡须食客的店内体验
improved the in-store Whiskerstay's experience,
古斯塔沃·弗林
首席执行官
洛博罗炸鸡
并提高了整个品牌的回头客数量
resulting in increased repeat business system-wide.
事实上  我们很高兴宣布
In fact, we are happy to share the news
牧歌电气
休斯顿
最新的全美顾客满意度指数调查
that the latest ACSI survey
显示胡须食客已跻身全国
now places Whiskerstay's in the top 10%
前10%的有限服务连锁店
of limited-service chains nationwide.
很好  珂丽奥  很好
Very nice, Cleo, very nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在有请古斯塔沃·弗林
And now let's hear from Gustavo Fring
洛博罗炸鸡的首席执行官
of Los Pollos Hermanos.
-谢谢  舒勒先生  -请吧
- Thank you, Herr Schuler. - Bitte.
我很高兴告诉各位
I am delighted to report
洛博罗炸鸡上一季度的收入
that the last quarter Los Pollos Hermanos revenues
增加了8.3%
have increased 8.3%.
同店销售额同比增长4.2%
Comparable restaurant sales increased by 4.2%,
已经连续八季度同店销售额增长
representing the eighth consecutive quarter of comparable sales increases.
除了继续做好我们的核心产品外
In addition to our continued focus on our core menu,
我们还很荣幸地介绍一款新产品
we are very proud to introduce a new offering
此产品将拓展我们的产品线
that will extend our product line
同时继续弘扬传统新墨西哥文化
while celebrating our traditional New Mexican culture.
我邀请各位品尝新出的"香辣扭扭薯条"
I invite you to taste our delicious "Spice Curls."
"西南风味的扭扭薯条"
"The curly fry with the Southwestern kick."
到了
Here we are.
厕所有地暖
The bathroom has heated floors.
开关就在电灯开关的下方
You'll find the dial just under the light switch.
还配有蒸汽淋浴房
There's a steam shower...
以及坐浴盆
and bidet.
这个能控制窗帘
This controls the drapes.
有许多客人喜欢观看牛仔竞技比赛
Many of our guests have enjoyed the rodeo.
明天在兰瑞特体育场就有
It's in town tomorrow at Reliant Stadium.
我非常推荐
I highly recommend it.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
我只住一晚
I'm only staying the night.
那就下次吧
Next time, then.
还有别的需要吗  先生
Is there anything else, sir?
不  不必了  就这样吧
No. No, no, that will be all.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
-谢谢  弗林先生  -不客气
- Thank you, Mr. Fring. - My pleasure.
请勿打扰
彼得
Peter. ‭
-你看谁来了  -谁
- Look who's here. - ‭Who?
你好啊  朋友
Hello, my friend.
古斯塔沃
Gustavo.
见到你我真高兴  朋友
It's good to see you, my friend.
你气色不错
Oh, you look well.
我不太舒服
Well, I don't feel well.
但是你来了我可能会好受一些
Maybe things will improve now that you're here.
莉迪亚告诉我塞拉曼加进监狱了
Lydia tells me Salamanca is in jail.
是不是你就能继续施工了
This means you can continue construction?
爱德华多·塞拉曼加因谋杀被捕了
E-Eduardo Salamanca has been arrested for murder.
然而  他在狱中也...不安分
However, even from jail he creates...issues.
怎么个不安分法儿
What kind of issues?
他让手下去烧我的一间餐馆
He ordered his men to burn down one of my restaurants.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
他在坐牢还能那么干
He's in jail. He can still do that?
恐怕是的
I'm afraid so.
我知道这不是我的专长领域
I know it's not exactly my area of expertise,
但监狱里不是总出人命吗
but don't people get killed in prison all the time?
"被捅死"  "被攮死"  一切死法皆有可能
I mean, "Shanked" and "Shivved" and whatnot?
塞拉曼加在国境这边出了事
Anything happens to Salamanca on this side of the border,
贩毒集团就会怪到我头上
the cartel will assume that it was my doing.
那意味着战争
It would mean war.
让我们措手不及的战争
War for which we are unprepared.
天啊
My God.
这噩梦还没完没了了
This nightmare never ends.
-他担心钱  -还"担心"
- He's concerned about the money. - ‭"Concerned"?!
四百八十万欧
4,800,000 Euros.
我没被抓简直是奇迹
It's a miracle I haven't been caught.
去年  审计员就差这么一点
Last year ‭the auditors came this close.
其中有个女的  我觉得她发现了
One of them, a woman -- I think she knew.
-彼得  -起初是一年
- Peter -- - At first it was a year.
然后两年  三年
Then it was two. Then three.
现在你告诉我...
And now you're telling me...
要多久
How long?
我等不了  等不了
I can't. I can't.
他们会抓到我  就全完了
They will catch me, and then it is over.
-彼得  -我等不了
- Peter -- - ‭I can't.
-彼得  -古斯塔沃  求你了
- Peter -- - Gustavo, please.
-我不能再等了  -听我说
- I can't. - ‭Listen to me.
-我...  -听我说
- I -- - ‭Listen to me.
你还记得圣地亚哥吗
Do you remember Santiago?
我们俩
The two of us.
我们被逼得走投无路
Our backs to the wall.
我永远不会忘记你当时做的
I will never forget what you did.
那个...
Oh, well...
你依然是当年那个你
You are still the same man.
必要之事你绝不含糊
You will do what is necessary.
坚强点  朋友
Stay strong, my friend.
我们都走到这一步了
We've come so far.
就差那么一丁点了
We are so very close.
好吧
Okay.
好
Good.
你用晚餐吧
Now...you eat.
明天我们去看牛仔竞技
Tomorrow you and I are going to the rodeo.
竞技
The rodeo?
对  去看牛仔
Yeah. To see the cowboys.
我还从来没去过呢
I've never been to the rodeo.
你会喜欢的
Well, ‭you're going to love it.
古斯塔沃
Gustavo.
-干杯  -干杯
- Prosit. - ‭Prosit.
干杯
Prost. ‭
"您的客人可在优雅的大房间内休憩
‭Uh, "Your guests will relax in the elegant great room,
房间内配有花岗岩石砌壁炉"
complete with soaring stone fireplace."
花岗岩
Soaring stone?
是啊  那是最优质的石材
Yeah. That's the best kind of stone.
一座薰衣草农场怎么样
How about a lavender farm?
真的吗
Seriously?
真的  附近有薰衣草
Yeah, well, it's, uh -- it's lavender-adjacent.
说详细点
Tell me more.
"将这神奇的土地当做自己的家
"Imagine a magical land called 'home.'
在乱花摇曳的微风中
Watch the sun set ‭across your own private meadow,
看日落余晖洒满你的私人牧场
as wild flowers sway in the breeze.
该精品沙漠会所
This stunning desert retreat
为您提供轻奢的生活格调"
promotes a casual ‭yet luxurious lifestyle."
我就是轻奢本人
I'm casual yet luxurious.
是  绝对的
Yeah. Totally.
还有五个车位的车库
It's got a five-car garage.
什么  那怎么行
What? How's that gonna work?
-我们一人只能有两台半车吗  -对
- We only get 2 1/2 cars each? - ‭Yeah.
垃圾
Garbage. ‭
野花在阳光下摇曳
So, that was wildflowers dancing in the sun?
在微风中摇曳
They're swaying in the breeze.
好吧
Oh. Okay.
不管怎样
Well, either way.
它们都挺开心的
They're having a very nice time.
索尔·古德曼  火速伸张正义
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you!
有话跟你说
I need a word.
有话  行
Oh. A word? Yeah, uh --
我也有话跟你说  "隧道"
Yeah, I have a word for you. Uh, "Tunnel"...
我现在就在隧道里
...which is where I am right now.
对不起  我听不清
Sorry! I can't hear you!
过会儿再打吧
Maybe try again later?
来了
Coming!
不管什么事
Whatever it is,
都不关我的事  也不关你的事
it's not for me, and it shouldn't be for you.
忘带钥匙了吗
Hey, forget your key --
好吧  进来吧
Okay. Yeah. Come right in.
就当自己家
Make yourself at home.
我还穿着内裤呢  别见外
You got me in my underwear, so enjoy the show.
你是爱德华多·塞拉曼加的代理律师
You're representing Eduardo Salamanca,
也就是豪尔赫·德古兹曼
AKA Jorge De Guzman.
对  他是我的委托人  怎么了
He is a client of mine, yeah. So?
我需要你给他保释出来
Well, I need you to get him out on bail.
等等  你怎么扯上拉罗·塞拉曼加的
Wait. What do you have to do with Lalo Salamanca?
我只是代表利益相关方
I represent someone who has an interest.
什么样的人
Someone like who?
不能让你委托人知道的人
Someone your client can never know about.
但是  我不接受神秘人士发号施令
Yeah, look, ‭I don't take marching orders from the man behind the curtain.
这个案子  你还是答应的好
In this case, it's better that you do.
你知道塞拉曼加都干过什么吧
You know what Salamanca did, right?
我知道
I am aware.
这是什么
What's this?
这是你完成任务所需的一切材料
This is everything you need to do your job.
弗雷德·惠伦
洛博罗炸鸡店
去吧
Go.
"与其所在当地社区关系密切"
"Significant ties to his local community"?
什么关系
What ties?
你们真的认为我会对你们的
Did you actually think I wasn't gonna hear
"私家侦探"毫不知情
about this "Private eye" of yours?
你说什么
Excuse me?
戴夫·克拉克
Dave Clark.
给你们关键目击证人做指导的神秘"第三方"
The mysterious "third party" who's coaching your key witness.
好吧
Alright, good.
行吧
You know what?
你们就继续装傻吧
Do the dumb act for Parson. Please.
我迫不及待想看他再整你们一次
I can't wait to see him rip you both a new one.
那个混蛋闹的是哪出
Any idea what that asshole is going on about?
我给图书管理员打电话
I'll call the librarian.
当着法官面好好表现  行吗
Uh, play to the judge, okay?
但是  别玩世不恭的
But don't -- don't, like, play to the judge.
千万不要
Don't over do it.
别太摆架子
Try not to be too cool.
谦逊点
I mean, look humble.
稍微胆怯点
A little bit scared.
没问题
No problem.
-是他们吗  -对
- Is that them? - ‭Yep.
那是谁
Who's that?
肯定是他的家人
That's gotta be his family.
弗雷德·惠伦
Fred Whalen.
差旅电汇的死者
The guy who died? At the Travel Wire?
听说你有新消息
And I'm told you have new information...
指控干扰证人
An allegation of witness tampering?
古德曼先生
Mr. Goodman?
没错  法官阁下
That's right, Your Honor.
干扰证人
Witness tampering.
我有理由认为
I have reason to believe
公诉方的关键证人
that the prosecution's key witness
受到了一名私家侦探的引导
was coached ‭by a private investigator
他受雇妨碍司法公正
who was hired to pervert justice.
公诉人有回应吗
Does the prosecution have a response?
很不幸  法官阁下
Unfortunately, Your Honor,
似乎有我们不知道的一位不明人士
it seems a person unknown to my team
可能与我们的证人有过接触
may have interacted with our witness,
让她打给罗伯茨警探
causing her to call Detective Roberts
并在最初审讯两个月后修改证词
and amend her statement two months after the initial interview.
我们最近才发现此事
This only recently came to our attention,
正在积极调查中
and we are vigorously investigating.
但愿如此
I would hope so.
话虽如此  法官阁下
Having said that, Your Honor,
这位证人只是本公诉案中很小的一环
this witness is one small element of the state's case.
鉴于犯罪情节极其暴力
In light of the extraordinary violence of the crime
以及德古兹曼先生为外籍人士
and the fact that Mr. De Guzman is a foreign national
与本地社区毫无关系
with no ties to the community,
我们请求法院将其视为潜逃风险
we ask that the court recognize him as a flight risk
同时也对新墨西哥州民众造成威胁
and as a danger to the citizens of New Mexico.
古德曼先生
Mr. Goodman?
恕我直言  法官阁下
Uh, all due respect, Your Honor,
这位证人不仅仅是本公诉案中
but the witness is not just one "Small element"
"很小的一环"
of the state's case.
她还是唯一能将德古兹曼先生
She's the only witness
与凶杀现场联系起来的证人
tying Mr. De Guzman to the murder scene,
而她受到了他人操控
and she's been manipulated.
此外  关于德古兹曼先生
Furthermore, the claim that Mr. De Guzman
与本地社区毫无关联的说法  显然是无稽之谈
has no ties to the community -- that's just patently false.
德古兹曼先生与阿尔布开克市有着深刻羁绊
Mr. De Guzman has deep ties to the city of Albuquerque.
我向您介绍  他的家人
I'd like you to meet... his family.
那是他的未婚妻
Uh, that's his fiancée
他的挚爱  贝丝·麦金农
and the love of his life, Beth McKinnon,
他的继子女  克里斯托弗和艾拉
his stepchildren, Christopher and Ella,
坐在他们身旁的是贝丝的母亲  玛丽
and sitting with them is Beth's mother, Mary.
法官阁下
Now, Your Honor,
这些孩子只有我委托人这一个父亲
my client is the only father that these kids have ever known.
他们都依靠他生活
They depend on him.
您怎么忍心
How can you possibly see fit
拆散这个美好的家庭呢
to separate this beautiful...family?
抱歉
Um...I'm sorry.
德古兹曼先生涉案的证词
The testimony, um, implicating Mr. De Guzman in this crime --
是捏造的
it's been fabricated.
您已经关押他三天时间
You've already held him for three days.
考虑到现有情况
Given the circumstances,
应该让德古兹曼先生获得保释
Mr. De Guzman should be granted bond.
法官阁下  请求私下磋商
Your Honor, a sidebar?
公诉方就没做好调查吗
Didn't the state do any investigating at all?
我们调查了  法官阁下
We did, Your Honor.
法官阁下  根据现有信息...
Your honor, ‭given what's transpired here...
行了  不用再说了
Alright, that's enough.
法官阁下  我真的...
Your Honor, I really --
我接受辩方观点  允许保释
I accept the defense's argument that bond is warranted.
但考虑到指控的严重性
But considering the severity of the charges,
我决定将保释金额设为七百万美元
I will set the amount at $7 million.
仅收现金
Cash only.
法官阁下...
Oh, Your Honor --
全体起立
All rise.
七百万
$7 million?
是的  我真的很抱歉
Yes, and I am so, so sorry.
我可以付
I can do that.
问题是
Thing is,
-你得去帮我取钱  -什么  我
- I'm gonna need you to pick it up. ‭- What? Me?
等我电话
I'll call you.
-你可以走了  -谢谢
- You're good to go. - Thank you.
吉米
Hey, Jimmy.
霍华德
Howard.
所以  工作的事你还在考虑吗
So...have you thought any more about the job?
工作
The job.
对啊
Yeah.
还没...
No, um...
我还在考虑
I'm still giving it some thought.
"还在考虑"
"Giving it some thought"?
是的
Yeah.
你知道吗
You know what?
不用再考虑了
Don't bother.
这个提议好像让你很生气
It seems I've upset you.
所以就此作罢吧
So offer's off the table.
让我很生气
You upset me?
怎么让我很生气了
How -- How'd you upset me?
你说呢
You tell me.
你有点奇怪啊  霍华德
This is getting a little weird, Howard.
你知道什么才叫"奇怪"吗
You want to know what's "Weird"?
你给一个人提供了工作机会
It's "Weird" to offer a job to a man
而作为回报  那个人却向你的汽车扔保龄球
and in return have bowling balls thrown at your car
在你工作午餐时派妓女来餐厅大闹
and prostitutes ‭sent to your business lunch.
这才叫"奇怪"
That's "Weird."
你在说什么呢
Are you listening to yourself?
我不知道你这些日子都经历了什么  霍华德
I don't know what you're into these days, Howard,
但是妓女  保龄球
but prostitutes and, uh, bowling balls?
你听起来有点不太正常
Uh...you sound unhinged.
吉米  我对你的痛苦深表遗憾
Jimmy, ‭I'm sorry you're in pain.
深表遗憾
You're sorry?
你害死了我哥哥  却对我说深表遗憾
You kill my brother, and you say you're sorry.
我告诉你吧
Let me tell you something.
那份工作  并没有让我生气
The job offer -- it didn't upset me.
反而让我觉得很好笑
It amused me.
赫赫有名的HHM律所里举足轻重的职位
Big job at the illustrious HHM.
有机会走上那么大的舞台
Chance to play at the palace?
就凭我这种小角色
Lil' ole me?
-我只是想  -你根本不知道外面在发生什么
- I was trying - You have no idea what's going on.
你是一个只活在自己的小世界里
You're a teensy tiny man
只关注自己的小人
in a teensy-weensy little bubble!
吉米啊
Oh, Jimmy.
快别他妈同情我了
Ohh, don't you fuckin' "Oh, Jimmy" me.
你有什么资格看不起我  可怜我
You look down on me?! You pity me?!
走就对了  霍华德
Walk away. That's right, Howard.
你知道我为什么不接受你的工作吗
You know why I didn't take the job?
因为它太渺小了
'Cause it's too small!
我不在乎这种工作
I don't care about it!
它对我来说屁都不是
It's nothing to me!
渺小到不能再渺小了
It's a bacterium!
我游走的世界大到你根本无法想像
I travel in worlds you can't even imagine!
你根本想像不到我的能力
You can't conceive of what I'm capable of!
我早就远远超越你了
I'm so far beyond you!
我是身着西装的上帝
I'm like a God in human clothing!
指尖射出闪电
Lightning bolts ‭shoot from my fingertips!